<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<helpIndex version="1.0">
  <tool name="PROGRAMMER" href="/index.htm#context/user/programming_a_device_using_the_programmer">
    <dialog name="Programmer_getting_started_dlg">     
	  <whatsthis name="create_a_new_project_from_a_scan">Scans the attached chain with the last used cable settings.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="create_a_new_blank_project">Creates a new blank project.</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="open_existing_programmer_project">Allows the user to browse to an existing .xcf configuration file and open an existing Programmer project.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="import_file_to_current_implementation">Imports the .xcf file into the current Diamond project.</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="Cable">Specifies the download cable type: Lattice (parallel port), USB (LSC USB cable), USB2 (FTDI USB2 cable), or Vantis.</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="Port">Specifies the serial port to which the download cable is connected. Select the port from the list or click Detect Cable.</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="Detect Cable">Automatically detects the parallel port to which the download cable is connected.</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
    <dialog name="BSCAN_configuration_dlg">
      <whatsthis name="bscan_config_type">Allows you to choose one of five BSCANs configuration types: BSCAN2 4 Port, BSCAN2 8 Port Asset Model, BSCAN2 8 Port JTAG/Corelis Model, BSCAN2 12 Port JTAG/Corelis Model, or BSCAN2 16 Port JTAG/Corelis Model.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="msports">Select the scan ports for the chains you want to access.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="leave_selected_ports_in">Select RTI, run test idle, to configure the BSCAN2. Selecting TLR, test logic rest, will remove the selected ports from the configuration. </whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="configure_ports">Scans the selected ports and displays the chains and devices for programming.
</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
    <dialog name="new_programmer_project_dlg">
      <whatsthis name="scan">Create a new project from a scan with default settings.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="custom_scan">Create a new project from a scan with custom settings.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="blank_programmer_project">Create a new programmer project.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="import_new_programmer_project_to_current_implementation">Allows the user to browse to an existing Diamond project and save the Programmer project as an .xcf file.</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="Cable">Specifies the download cable type: Lattice (parallel port), USB (LSC USB cable), USB2 (FTDI USB2 cable), or Vantis.</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="Port">Specifies the serial port to which the download cable is connected. Select the port from the list or click Detect Cable.</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="Detect Cable">Automatically detects the parallel port to which the download cable is connected.</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
    <dialog name="general_settings_dlg">
      <whatsthis name="at_programmer_startup">Alllows you to select between showing the Programmer Getting Started dialog box at start-up, or opening the last Programmer proejct at start-up.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="log_file_path">Shows the location of the Programmer log file.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="USERCODE Display">Allows the user to choose in which format the USERCODE will be displayed.  Choices are Hex, ASCII, and Decimal.</whatsthis>   
    </dialog>
    <dialog name="programming_settings_dlg">
      <whatsthis name="turbo_mode">Programs all the devices on the board in parallel. If an Operation Override is selected, all Operation descriptions in the chain file are temporarily changed to the override setting.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="sequential_mode">Programs all the devices on the board one at a time. If an Operation Override is selected, all Operation descriptions in the chain file are temporarily changed to the override setting.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="use_default_jtag_states">Uses Test-Logic-Reset (TLR) as the starting and ending JTAG state of the JTAG State Machine for download.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="avoid_test_logic_reset_state">Avoids the Test Logic Reset State of the JTAG State Machine during download.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="use_custom_jtag_states">Specify Test-Logic-Reset (TLR) or Run-Test/Idle (RTI) as the starting and ending JTAG state of the JTAG State Machine for download.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="initial_tap_state">Specify TLR or RTI as the starting JTAG state of the JTAG State Machine for download.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="final_tap_state">Specify TLR or RTI as the ending JTAG state of the JTAG State Machine for download.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="use_default_pulse_width_delay">Uses the fastest TCK clock speed.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="use_custom_pulse_width_delay">Enables the Use Custome Pulse Width Delay feature.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="tck_low_pulse_width_delay">Allows you to slow down the TCK clock. This is done by extending the low period of the clock.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="check_cable_setup_before_programming">Confirms that the cable signals are correctly connected to the board and devices in the JTAG chain on the board match the devices selected in the .xcf file.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="continue_download_on_error">Ignores any errors while downloading and continues running.</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
    <dialog name="cable_io_settings_dlg">
      <whatsthis name="detect_cable">Automatically detects the parallel port to which the download cable is connected. This feature works only with a Lattice ispDOWNLOAD cable, not a Vantis cable.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="cable">Specifies the download cable type: Lattice (parallel port), USB (LSC USB cable), USB2 (FTDI USB2 cable), or Vantis.
</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="port">Specifies the port to which the download cable is connected.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="custom_port">Specifies a custom parallel port to which the download cable is connected. Use hexadecimal format to type the port name.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="use_default_io_settings">Only use the four JTAG signals.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="use_custom_io_settings">Specify additional non-JTAG signals connected to the board</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="initn_pin_connected">Select this option if you connect the INIT pin to the download cable. This option is only available with the ispDOWNLOAD USB cable.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="done_pin_connected">Select this option if you connect the DONE pin to the download cable. This option is only available with the ispDOWNLOAD USB cable.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="trst_reset_pin_connected">Select this option if you connect the TRST pin to the download cable. Specify active high or active low.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="programn_pin_connected">Select this option if you connect the PROGRAMN pin to the download cable.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="ispen_bscan_pin_connected">Select this option if you connect the ispEN/BSCAN pin to the download cable. Specify active high or active low.</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
    <dialog name="device_properties_dlg">
      <whatsthis name="access_mode">Selects the mode for programming the device.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="operation">Lists the available operation modes for the device. Select one from the drop-down list.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="programming_file">Selects the data file for programming or verify.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="tck_frequency">Specifies the TCK clock frequency for the chosen device. This value is used to determine the TCK clock period and the length of the delay times.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="svf_vendor">Select the SVF vendor for the chosen device.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="instruction_register_length">Specify the instruction register length for putting the device into BYPASS during programming. The software automatically fills in this box when you select a BSDL file. You must enter the instruction register length for a JTAG-NOP device if a BSDL file is not selected.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="load_from_file">Import the IR length from a BSDL or SVF file.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="reinitialize_part_on_program_error">Reinitializes the device to its blank, or erased, state when a programming error occurs.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="verify_readback_mask_bitstream_file">Select a custom verify mask file.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="use_svf_interpreter">Use SVF interpreter.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="use_ispvm_interpreter">Use ispVM interpeter.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="use_usercode_from_programming_file">Program the USERCODE register with the value in the data file. </whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="use_override_usercode">Do not program the USERCODE register with the value in the data file. Specify a value instead.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="usercode_hex">USERCODE value (in Hex) to be programmed into the USERCODE register.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="autoincrement_after_program">Automatically increment the USERCODE value after programming.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="increment_value">Amount to increment the USERCODE value after programming.</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="family">Select an external memory family from the drop-down list.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="vendor">Select an external memory vendor from the drop-down list.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="device">Select an external memory device from the drop-down list.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="package">Select an external memory package from the drop-down list.</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="operation">Select the operation mode. The default is Erase, Program, Verify.</whatsthis>	  
	  <whatsthis name="fpga_loader_data_file">Browse to FPGA Loader Data (.jed) file.  Non-volatile devices only.</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="flash_data_file">Browse to Flash Data file.  Non-volatile devices only.</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="data_file_size">Displays the full file size. You can change this size by typing a different file size. This feature is useful if you only want to use a portion of the file for the operation. If you change the file size, it must be no larger than the full file size or the device size.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="start_address">Displays the start address of the flash device. For the AMD parallel flash, the starting address is automatically selected and cannot be changed.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="end_address">Displays the end address of the flash.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="erase_spi_on_programming_error">Erases the flash device if a verify error occurs.</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="secure_spi_flash_golden_pattern_sectors">Allows user to secure second half of SPI Flash to secure golden pattern.  Available only on devices that support this secure feature.</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="enter_key">Enter encryption key.</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="confirm_key">Confirm encryption key.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="load_key">Load an encyprtion key from an external file.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="save_key">Save encyrption key to external file.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="format">Choose between ASCII or Hex key display.</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="show_key">Toggles display of key.</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="device_description">Displays the BSDL file entry name.  This field is editable.</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="instruction_register_length">Displays pre-assigned instruction register length.  Not editable.</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="bypass_instruction">Displays pre-assigned bypass instruction.  Not editable.</whatsthis>
	</dialog>	
	<dialog name="status_register_dlg">
      <whatsthis name="Refresh">Refreshes status of the device.</whatsthis>
      </dialog>	  
	  <dialog name="edit_io_status_dlg">
      <whatsthis name="io_state">Select the desired I/O state.</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="bsdl_file">Browse to the desired .bsm file. A BSDL file, which is the acronym for Boundary Scan Description Language file, is a subset of Very High Speed IC Hardware Description Language (VHDL) that describes the boundary scan device package, pin description and boundary scan cell of the input and output pins. The BSDL file is very important in generating a boundary scan test. Without a BSDL file, it is impossible to generate any boundary scan test</whatsthis>      
	  <whatsthis name="read_io_state">Click to read I/O state.  A BSDL must be selected and a device and board must be connected to the computer.  Refer to the online help for more information.</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="package">The target device package.</whatsthis>  
	  </dialog>	  	  
	  <dialog name="edit_custom_dlg">
      <whatsthis name="device_family">Dropdown list of custom device families.</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="device">The name that was assigned to the device.</whatsthis>      
	  <whatsthis name="package">The name that was assigned to the package.</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="device_description">The description that was assigned to the device.</whatsthis>
	</dialog>	  
	  <dialog name="custom_spi_flash_dlg">
      <whatsthis name="device_family">Edit box of custom device families.</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="device_description">The description that was assigned to the device.</whatsthis>      
	  <whatsthis name="device_name_package">This can be any alpha-numeric string that describes the device name (for example: SPI-M25P32).</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="package">This can be any alpha-numeric string that describes the package (for example: 16-pin SOIC).</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="device_vendor">The vendor of the custom SPI Flash device.</whatsthis> 
	  <whatsthis name="device_density">Allows you to select device density.  Available densities range from 512 Kbits to 256 Mbits.</whatsthis> 
	  <whatsthis name="device_id">This can be any alpha-numeric string that describes the device ID (for example: 0x15).</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="byte_per_sector">Allows you to choose desired bytes per sector value from dropdown.</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="protection_options_on">If the SPI Flash device supports sector protection, check this box to enable protection options.</whatsthis>
	</dialog>
  
	<dialog name="custom_device_information_dlg">
      <whatsthis name="device_name">Edit box limited to 12 characters maximum. Valid characters are alphanumeric and a dash.</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="device_full_name">Edit box limited to 12 characters maximum. Valid characters are alphanumeric and a dash.</whatsthis>      
	  <whatsthis name="package">This can be any alpha-numeric string that describes the package (for example: 16-pin SOIC).</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="id_length">ID length equal to 32, per IEEE 1149.1 Std. This box is not editable.</whatsthis> 
	  <whatsthis name="device_id">Limited to four hexadecimal characters. Valid characters are "Ox" followed by two hexadecimal characters.  Default value is "OxFFFFFFFF".</whatsthis> 
	  <whatsthis name="instruction_register_length">Select any number ranging from 2 to 32.</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="read_id_instruction">Must be entered in binary only (0 or 1). The number of characters entered is limited to the Instruction Register Length.</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="instruction_bypass_pattern">Must be entered in binary only (0 or 1). The number of characters entered is limited to the Instruction Register Length.</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="bsdl_file">Browse to the desired .bsm file. A BSDL file, which is the acronym for Boundary Scan Description Language file, is a subset of Very High Speed IC Hardware Description Language (VHDL) that describes the boundary scan device package, pin description and boundary scan cell of the input and output pins. The BSDL file is very important in generating a boundary scan test. Without a BSDL file, it is impossible to generate any boundary scan test.</whatsthis>    
	</dialog>	
		  
	<dialog name="cable_signal_tests_dlg">
      <whatsthis name="toggle">Alternates between log 1, logic 0, and logic 1.</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="hold_high">Holds at logic 1.</whatsthis>      
	  <whatsthis name="hold_low">Holds at logic 0.</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="read">(TDO Only). Reads back the data from TDO and records the read back data in the Programmer log file</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="test">Applies the selected settings to the selected pin connections. This causes the pins that have a toggle setting to toggle once from logic 1 to logic 0 to logic 1.</whatsthis> 
	  <whatsthis name="loop_test">Performs continuous testing, causing the pins that have a toggle setting to toggle continuously until you click ESC.</whatsthis> 
	  <whatsthis name="view_log">Opens the log file, an ASCII text file that summarizes the results of the Cable Signal Test operations.</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="power_check">Tests the cable and power connections, causing the VCC Status LED to blink green or red to indicate that cable and power are detected or not detected.</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="vcc_status">Shows the status of the cable and power connection. The LED blinks green when the cable and power are detected. It blinks red and produces an error message when cable or power is not detected.</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="toggle_delay">Sets the delay after each operation. Default is 0.</whatsthis>    
	  <whatsthis name="number_of_bytes">Sets the number of bytes read by each operation. Default is 0.</whatsthis>
	</dialog>	
		
  </tool>  
  <tool name="Deployment Tool" href="/index.htm#context/user/Deployment_Tool">
  <dialog name="Deployment_Tool_getting_started_dlg">
     
	  <whatsthis name="function_type">Choose Tester, Embedded System, or External Memory</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="output_file_type">Choose output file type.  Output file types are dependent on Function Type.</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="open_existing_deployment">Clock to open an existing Deployment Tool File (.ddt). </whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="recent_files">Dropdown list of recent Deployment Tool Files (.ddt).</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
	</tool> 
  
  
  <tool name="Debugger" href="/index.htm#context/user/Debugging_Files">
  <dialog name="debugger_cable_io_port_setup">      
      <whatsthis name="cable_description">This option is displayed when multiple cables are detected.  When enabled, this option allows you to select the desired cable.</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="cable">Specifies the download cable type: Lattice (parallel port), USB (LSC USB cable), or USB2 (FTDI USB2 cable).</whatsthis>	  
      <whatsthis name="port">Specifies the port to which the download cable is connected.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="custom_port">Specifies a custom parallel port to which the download cable is connected. Use hexadecimal format to type the port name.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="using_slave_spi_interface_connection">This option allows you to target the slave SPI port of the selected device.  This allows you to debug slave SPI device programming.</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="use_default_io_settings">Only use the four JTAG signals.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="use_custom_io_settings">Specify additional non-JTAG signals connected to the board</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="initn_pin_connected">Select this option if you connect the INIT pin to the download cable. This option is only available with the ispDOWNLOAD USB cable.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="done_pin_connected">Select this option if you connect the DONE pin to the download cable. This option is only available with the ispDOWNLOAD USB cable.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="trst_reset_pin_connected">Select this option if you connect the TRST pin to the download cable. Specify active high or active low.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="programn_pin_connected">Select this option if you connect the PROGRAMN pin to the download cable.</whatsthis>
	   <whatsthis name="ispen_pin_connected">Select this option if you connect the ispEN pin to the download cable. Specify active high or active low.</whatsthis>
  </dialog>
  <dialog name="debugger_options">
	  <whatsthis name="log">Allows you to specify name and location of log file.</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="clear_this_log_file_each_time_start_application">Check to clear the log file each time Debugger is started.</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="source_editor">Allows you to specify font, size, tab size, of Source Editor.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="show_the_number">Toggles display of line numbers in left margin of Source Editor.</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="show_indicator_margin">Toggles display of indicator margin in left side of Source Editor.</whatsthis>      
      <whatsthis name="disable_svf_syntax_checker">Disables the tool that checks the syntax of the SVF file.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="ignore_ir_and_dr_header_trailer_in_svf">Ignores the HIR, TIR, HDR, and TDR information in SVF file. If you set up HIR, TIR, HDR, or TDR in this dialog box, this option must be selected.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="continue_on_error">Continues processing the file even if there is an error. You can look at the log file for the errors encountered. When this option is selected, the log file also reports state machine transitions and delay time for debug.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="mixed_chain">Tells the Debugger that the hardware configuration is a mixed chain, therefore disabling the ISP chain when processing the SVF file.</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="svf_tck_frequency">Specifies the TCK clock frequency for the chosen SVF file. This value is used to determine the TCK clock period and the length of the delay times.</whatsthis>	  
	  <whatsthis name="svf_vendor">Allows you select from the following SVF vendors for the selected device: JTAG STANDARD, LATTICE, ALTERA, and XILINX. This option is available for JTAG devices only.</whatsthis>	  	  
      <whatsthis name="instruction_register_header">Sets the IR header length in number of bits (0-100).</whatsthis>	  
	  <whatsthis name="instruction_register_trailer">Sets the IR trailer length in number of bits (0-100).</whatsthis>	  
      <whatsthis name="data_register_header">Sets the HDR in number of bits (0-100).</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="data_register_trailer">Sets the TDR in number of bits (0-100).</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="ignore_ir_and_dr_header_trailer_in_stapl">Ignores the HIR, TIR, HDR and TDR information in STAPL file. If you set up HIR, TIR, HDR, or TDR in this dialog box, this option must be selected.</whatsthis>
	  <whatsthis name="starting_tap_state">Select the starting JTAG state of the JTAG State Machine for download. Only two states are available: TLR (Test-Logic-Reset) and RTI (Run-Test/Idle).</whatsthis>  
  </dialog>
  </tool>  
  
  <tool name="Model 300" href="/index.htm#context/user/using_the_model_300_programmer">  
	</tool> 
	
	<tool name="Programming File Utiity" href="/index.htm#context/user/Using_Programming_File_Utility">  
	</tool> 
  
</helpIndex>
