<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<helpIndex version="1.0">
  <tool name="schlib_manager" href="/index.htm#context/user/using_lattice_fpga_symbol_library">
    <dialog name="copy_symbols">
      <whatsthis name="from_library_to">&lt;b&gt;From library&lt;/b&gt; - Displays the current library.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;To&lt;/b&gt; - Type the name for the destination library. You can also select an open library from the drop-down list.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="folders">Click the Folders button to browse for the library folders.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="libraries">Click the Libraries button to browse for the compressed library.</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
    <dialog name="extract_symbols">
      <whatsthis name="from_library_to">&lt;b&gt;Form library&lt;/b&gt; - Displays the current library.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;To&lt;/b&gt; - Type the name for the destination folder. You can also select a folder by clicking the Folders button.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="folders">Click the Folders button to browse for the library folder.</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
    <dialog name="find_symbols">
      <whatsthis name="find_symbols_find">Type the name of the symbol you want to find and click the Find button. You may also type wildcards, if you do not know the precise name of the file. After you click the Find button, a message box will pop up telling you the result of finding. The found symbols will be highlighted in the Library Manager.</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
    <dialog name="find_symbols_in_libraries">
      <whatsthis name="find_symbols">Type the name of the symbol you want to find. You may type wildcards if you do not know the precise name of the file.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="look_in">&lt;b&gt;All symbol library search paths&lt;/b&gt; - Select this option to search for the specified symbols in the symbol library search paths.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;In folder&lt;/b&gt; - Select this option to search for the specified symbols in a particular folder or library. Type the name of the folder or library in the edit box. If you enter the name of a binary library, only that library will be searched. If you enter the name of a folder, that folder and any binary library in that folder will be searched.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Look in all sub-folders&lt;/b&gt; - Select this option to look in all sub-folders of the specified folder.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Browse&lt;/b&gt; - You can also click the Browse button to browse for the folder.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="find">Click the Find button to search for the specified symbols. A message box will pop up telling you the result of finding. The found symbols will be highlighted in the Library Manager window.</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
    <dialog name="open_from_search_paths">
      <whatsthis name="symbol_library_search_paths">The list box lists all the symbol libraries in your search paths. Select one from the list and click the OK button. The selected library will be opened in the Library Manager with the first symbol in the library selected.</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
    <dialog name="rename_symbol">
      <whatsthis name="from_to">Type the new name for the selected symbol and click the OK button, the new name will be accepted.</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
  </tool>
</helpIndex>