<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<helpIndex version="1.0">
  <tool name="sym_editor" href="/index.htm#context/user/creating_schematic_symbols">
    <dialog name="symbol_type">
      <whatsthis name="select_type">Specifies symbol type for the current symbol.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Cell&lt;/b&gt; - Cell symbols represent the primitive cells (transistors, resistors, diodes, and so on) used to design integrated circuits. The pins on Cell symbols are named for identification in netlists.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Block&lt;/b&gt; - Block symbols are used to build a hierarchical design. A Block symbol represents a schematic or HDL module at the next-lower level of the hierarchy. Bus pins are permitted on Block symbols.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Graphic&lt;/b&gt; - Graphic symbols add information that is not part of the circuitry. Graphic symbols are typically used for tables and notes. No pins are associated with Graphic symbols, and they are never included in the hierarchy or netlists.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Master&lt;/b&gt; - Master symbols are used for title blocks, logos, revision blocks, and other standardized graphic symbols. You can add text to a Master symbol to display the company name, address, project description, date, and so on. </whatsthis>
    </dialog>
    <dialog name="object_properties">
      <whatsthis name="object_list">Lists the current symbol and the pins that are selected in the Symbol Editor window. Click Symbol Attributes or a pin name in the list to show the available attributes in the right-hand table.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="filter">Limits the attributes displayed in the table below it. Type a string (wildcards are supported) that includes the characters you want to include and click &lt;b&gt;Go&lt;/b&gt;. To recover the original list, erase the string in the edit box and click &lt;b&gt;Go&lt;/b&gt;. </whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="attribute_list">Lists the available attributes for the symbol or pin selected in the left-hand Object List. The attributes are listed in alphabetical order. To specify an attribute value, double-click the Value cell, enter the new value, and click &lt;b&gt;Apply&lt;/b&gt;.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="name_location">Controls the pin name position relative to the selected pin.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Left&lt;/b&gt; - Displays the pin name to the left of the pin.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Top&lt;/b&gt; - Displays the pin name above the pin.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Right&lt;/b&gt; - Displays the pin name to the right of the pin.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Bottom&lt;/b&gt; - Displays the pin name below the pin.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Vertical&lt;/b&gt; - Displays the pin name as vertical text.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Offset&lt;/b&gt; - Specifies the distance of the pin name from the pin. Type an offset value in this edit box.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="clear">Clears the selected attribute value.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="reset">Resets the selected attribute to its original value.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="apply">Applies the attribute settings in this dialog box.</whatsthis>
    
	  <description name="BBOX" href="">Indicates the bounding box or the area for a given UGROUP. Given in number of rows and columns. Convention: BBOX= H,W</description>
	  <description name="BBOXTYPE" href="">Obsolete. Do not use.</description>
	  <description name="black_box" href="">Tells Precision RTL Synthesis that the module should not be compiled or optimized. Only the interface need be defined for synthesis.</description>
	  <description name="COARSE" href="">Attach to a DELAY element to set a coarse delay with CDEL delay parameters.</description>
	  <description name="COMP" href="">Attach to a block, to specify a name for the device component that is created when the block is mapped. Convention: COMP(PLC)=comp_name</description>
	  <description name="DCSMODE" href="">Attach to a DCS element to set the mode.</description>
	  <description name="DELAYTYPE" href="">Specifies the delay type on the DELAY element.</description>
	  <description name="DIFFCURRENT" href="">The differential current-source type driver has programmable output current in each mode of operation.</description>
	  <description name="DIFFRESISTOR" href="">Attach to input or output buffers (such as IB or OB) to provide differential termination.</description>
	  <description name="DIN" href="">Instructs map to pack a DIN/DOUT register into PIO/IOLOGIC sites. Convention: DIN= signal_name</description>
	  <description name="donot_touch" href="">Tells Precision RTL Synthesis to pass the module through synthesis without optimizing or unmapping.</description>
	  <description name="DOUT" href="">Instructs map to pack a DIN/DOUT register into PIO/IOLOGIC sites. Convention: DOUT= signal_name</description>
	  <description name="ENDPOINT" href="">Obsolete. Use Spreadsheet View to apply the TO keyword in the BLOCK, MAXDELAY, and MULTICYCLE constraints instead.</description>
	  <description name="FINE" href="">Attach to a DELAY element to set a fine delay with FDEL delay parameters.</description>
	  <description name="GSR" href="">Enables or disables the global set/reset for registered elements such as registers, PLLs, and memories.</description>
	  <description name="HGROUP" href="">Group components that are to be instantiated multiple times. Convention: HGROUP= identifier</description>
	  <description name="hierarchy" href="">Tells Precision RTL Synthesis to maintain the hierarchy of the module.</description>
	  <description name="HULOC" href="">Indicates the physical location of the northwest corner of an HGROUP or UGROUP assignment. Convention: HULOC = row#col#</description>
	  <description name="HURLOC" href="">Indicates the northwest corner of a region for a given HGROUP or UGROUP definition. Convention: HURLOC = row#col#</description>
	  <description name="IMPEDANCE" href="">Sets the on-chip programmable output impedance.</description>
	  <description name="IMPEDANCEGND" href="">Attach to output and bidirectional buffers to connect to ground.</description>
	  <description name="IMPEDANCEVCCIO" href="">Attach to output and bidirectional buffers to connect to high.</description>
	  <description name="INBUF" href="">INBUF is a global setting. All unused input buffers are disabled when INBUF is OFF to save power.</description>
	  <description name="LOAD" href="">Attach to an output buffer to modify loading on outputs from the default 50 pF for timing analysis. Convention: LOAD= xx.xx</description>
	  <description name="LOC" href="">Specifies a site location for the component that is created when this block is mapped. Convention: LOC= site_name</description>
	  <description name="noopt" href="">Tells Precision RTL Synthesis that an instance should not be optimized or changed.</description>
	  <description name="NORETIME" href="">Prevents re-timing on the hierarchy of the instance. Convention: NORETIME= string</description>
	  <description name="PWRSAVE" href="">Attach to input combinations to reduce the common mode range.</description>
	  <description name="RBBOX" href="">Indicates the area of a region. Convention: RBBOX = H,W</description>
	  <description name="REFCIRCUIT" href="">Allows you to choose this internal reference circuit or an external one.</description>
	  <description name="REGION" href="">Indicates the region to which a given HGROUP or UGROUP belongs. Convention: REGION = identifier</description>
	  <description name="SCHMITT_TRIGGER" href="">Obsolete. Do not use.</description>
	  <description name="SLEW" href="">Attach to an output buffer or pad to specify the relative speed (slew rate) of the output driver, with 1 indicating the slowest and 100 the fastest.</description>
	  <description name="syn_black_box" href="">Tells Synplify Pro to treat the module as a black box during synthesis.</description>
	  <description name="syn_hier" href="">Tells Synplify Pro how to control the amount of hierarchical transformation that occurs across boundaries on module or component instances during optimization.</description>

	  <description name="syn_netlist_hierarc" href="">Tells Synplify Pro whether or not to generate the hierarchy in the EDIF output when assigned to the top-level module of your design. The default (true) is to allow hierarchy generation.</description>
	  <description name="syn_noarrayports" href="">Tells Synplify Pro to treat the ports of a design unit as individual signals (scalars), not as buses (arrays) in the EDIF file.</description>
	  <description name="syn_noprune" href="">Tells Synplify Pro whether or not to remove instances that have outputs that are not driven.</description>
	  <description name="TERMINATEGND" href="">This attribute determines the on-chip parallel input and output termination.</description>
	  <description name="TERMINATEVCCIO" href="">This attribute determines the on-chip parallel input and output termination.</description>
	  <description name="TERMINATEVTT" href="">This attribute sets the on-chip input parallel termination to VTT.</description>
	  <description name="UGROUP" href="">Universal grouping construct.Convention:UGROUP = identifier</description>
	  <description name="VCMT" href="">Attached to input buffer elements (e.g., IB), assigning value types allows you to enable a common mode voltage, that is, choose between common mode termination or VTT termination.</description>
	</dialog>
    <dialog name="options">
      <whatsthis name="show_grid">Controls whether the Grid is displayed. The grid appears as dots, with one dot at every grid intersection. Every tenth grid point is larger. As you zoom out and the grid points get closer, some grid dots might not be displayed.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="use_wide_line">There are two line weights for drawing lines and rectangles. Select this option to use the heavier weight in your drawing. Wide lines have the same weight as buses on schematics.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="default_symbol_type">Specifies the default symbol type. The selected type will be the default symbol created every time you start the Symbol Editor. </whatsthis>
    </dialog>
  </tool>
</helpIndex>