<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<helpIndex version="1.0">
  <tool name="WAVE_EDITOR" href="/index.htm#context/user/about_wet">
    <view name="wave_display" href="/index.htm#context/user/about_wet" />
    <view name="WAVEFORM_PROPERTY" href="/index.htm#context/user/setting_node_parameters" />
    <view name="PULSE_PROPERTY" href="/index.htm#context/user/setting_pulse_state_and_duration" />
    <view name="insert_pattern" href="/index.htm#context/user/creating_and_using_patterns" />
    <dialog name="export_wave" href="/index.htm#context/user/exporting_waveform_stimulus">
      <whatsthis name="export_type">Enables you to select an export format. This appends the appropriate file extension to the output file.</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
    <dialog name="add_wave" href="/index.htm#context/user/creating_waveforms">
      <whatsthis name="polarity">Enables you to select the polarity for the signal you want to add.</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
    <dialog name="import_wave" href="/index.htm#context/user/importing_signal_names">
      <whatsthis name="filter">These checkboxes are used to filter the signals listed in the Imported Wave list box. You can clear any of the options to narrow your choices.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="imported_wave">Lists the available signals contained in the specified .naf file.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="browse">Opens a dialog box. You can select a .naf file in that dialog box and click &lt;b&gt;Open&lt;/b&gt;. The signals contained in the .naf file will be listed in the Imported Wave list box.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="arrows">&lt;b&gt;&gt;&lt;/b&gt; - Adds the signals selected in the Imported Wave list box to the Selected Wave list box.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;&gt;&gt;&lt;/b&gt; - Adds all the signals listed in the Imported Wave list box to the Selected Wave list box.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;&lt;&lt;/b&gt; - Deletes the signals selected in the Selected Wave list box.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;&lt;&lt;&lt;/b&gt; - Clears all the signals listed in the Selected Wave list box.<!--This is hard-coded due to special character support. Let developer change code if this needs to be modified.--></whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="selected_wave">Lists the signal names you want to add to the Waveform Editor window.</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
    <dialog name="show_wave" href="/index.htm#context/user/wavedit_showing_waveforms"></dialog>
    <dialog name="remove_wave" href="/index.htm#context/user/wavedit_deleting_cutting_copying_and_pasting"></dialog>
    <dialog name="time_setting" href="/index.htm#context/user/setting_simulation_time_unit">
      <whatsthis name="time_unit">Specifies the time units.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
You can use the two boxes to select the time interval for the simulation database. In the simulation stimulus file, stimulus values are specified at intervals of this Time Unit.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
All stimulus events occur at, and have lengths of, integral multiples of the Time Unit. This feature makes it easier to draw waveforms because all Transitions are automatically forced to occur at multiples of the Time Unit.</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
    <dialog name="page_setup" href="/index.htm#context/user/about_wet">
      <whatsthis name="print_range">&lt;b&gt;Print All&lt;/b&gt; - Prints the entire waveforms.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Print Current Range&lt;/b&gt; - Prints the current waveform display.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Print Customized Range&lt;/b&gt; - Prints a portion of the waveforms. Use the Start Time and End Time boxes to specify the time at which the plot is to begin and to finish.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="time_scale">Specifies the scale of plot. Changing the time scale changes the number of pages required to print the waveform. This option is unavailable if &lt;b&gt;Fit Page&lt;/b&gt; is selected.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="print_name">Prints the Names strip on every page. If this option is cleared, only the first sheet displays the names of waveforms, allowing more display space on the following sheets.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="print_ruler">Prints the ruler together with the waveforms.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="fit_page">Reduces or enlarges the waveforms so that they fit one printed page.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="system_page_setup">Opens the system Page Setup dialog box.</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
    <dialog name="options">
      <whatsthis name="bus_radix">Specifies Bus Radix mode as Binary, Octal, Decimal or Hex.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="show_grid_lines">Draws the waveforms with dotted lines separating them. These lines make it easier to see which waveform you are about to select before you click.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="auto_save">Specifies the time interval for the auto-save function. You can select &lt;b&gt;Never Auto Save&lt;/b&gt; to cancel the function.</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
  </tool>
</helpIndex>