<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<helpIndex version="1.0">
  <tool name="SPREADSHEET_VIEW" href="/index.htm#context/user/spreadsheet_view">
    <view name="SSHVIEW_PORTASSIGN_VIEW" href="/index.htm#context/user/assigning_pin_locations" />
    <view name="SSHVIEW_PINASSIGN_VIEW" href="/index.htm#context/user/assigning_pin_locations" />
    <view name="SSHVIEW_CLKRES_VIEW" href="/index.htm#context/user/setting_clock_attributes" />
    <view name="SSHVIEW_ROUTEPRI_VIEW" href="/index.htm#context/user/assigning_route_priorities" />
    <view name="SSHVIEW_CELLMAP_VIEW" href="/index.htm#context/user/Specifying_Registers_for_Flip-flops" />
    <view name="SSHVIEW_GLOBAL_VIEW" href="/index.htm#context/user/setting_global_preferences" />
    <view name="SSHVIEW_TIMING_VIEW" href="/index.htm#context/user/setting_timing_preferences" />
    <view name="SSHVIEW_GROUP_VIEW" href="/index.htm#context/user/grouping_logical_components" />
    <view name="SSHVIEW_MISC_VIEW" href="/index.htm#context/user/setting_misc_prefs" />
    <dialog name="assignpin" href="/index.htm#context/user/assigning_pin_locations">
      <whatsthis name="signal_list_pane">
Port type and signal name for each of the ports that were selected from the Port Attributes sheet. </whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="pin_list_pane">
List of available pins. Selected pins for the signals to be assigned are displayed in bold. By default, the pins listed at the top of the list are selected and listed in sequential order. When you select a pin name from the list, the pins following it are selected for the same number of signals to be assigned. </whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="clock">DQS, PLL/DLL, MCA, MPI, SERDES or Primary Clock input, output, or I/O pins.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="i_o_only">All user-programmable I/O pins that can only be used for input and output.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="mpi">Pins that support a multiple processor interface.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="dedicated">Dedicated pins that support signal assignments. The software supports the assignment of user-defined signals to a subset of dedicated device pins. In general, the software does not require that you assign signals to dedicated pins.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="sysconfig">Dual-purpose configuration pins.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="mca">Pins that support multiple chip alignment.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="dont_care">Includes all LVDS pins.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="true_pside_pin">Positive Differential (T) LVDS input or driver pins for true differential pins.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="true_nside_pin">Negative Differential (C) LVDS input or driver pins for true differential pins.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="emulated_pside_pin">Positive Differential (T) LVDS input or driver pins for emulated differential pins.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="emulated_nside_pin">Negative Differential (C) LVDS input or driver pins for emulated differential pins.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="auto_sort">
Automatically sorts the pins based on the selected "Sort by" options. 
      </whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="manual_sort">
Turns off the automatic "Sort by" options and allows you to drag selected pins to adjust the pin order. Select the desired pin types from the upper right pane, and then click Manual Sort. Afterwards, click a pin and drag it to the desired position.
      </whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="sort_by_package_column">Sorts the available pins list by column, in a left-right package orientataion.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="sort_by_package_row">Sorts the available pins list by row, in a top-bottom package orientation.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="sort_by_pin_number">Sorts the available pins list by pin number.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="sort_by_pad_name">Sorts the available pins list by pad name.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="sort_in_bank">Sorts the available pins list by name or number bank-by-bank.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="ascending">Applies an A-Z order to the available pins list.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="descending">Applies a Z-A order to the available pins list.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="assign_pins">
Assigns the pins according to the option selected from the Assign drop-down menu.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="assign_every">Changes the number of pins displayed on the available pins list, enabling you to assign every pin or assign every other, second, third or fourth pin.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="check_pins">
Checks the validity of the sequence of selected pins and corresponding signals. Displays an error message for each invalid assignment.</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
    <dialog name="assignsig" href="/index.htm#context/user/assigning_pin_locations">
      <whatsthis name="pin_list_pane">
The list of pins that were selected from the Pin Assignments sheet.      </whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="signal_list_pane">List of available signals. Selected signals for the pins to be assigned are displayed in bold. By default, the signals at the top of the list are selected and listed in sequential order. When you select a signal name from the list, the signals following it are selected for the same number of pins to be assigned. Selecting more than one type from Signal Types combines the types that are listed.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="clock">Displays all clock ports in the signals list.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="input">Displays all input ports in the signals list, including clock input ports.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="output">Displays all output ports in the signals list.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="bi_dir">Displays all bi-directional ports in the signals list.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="enable_filter_string">Enables you to narrow the signals list to those signals that begin with the same letters. Type the first few letters of signal names, followed by an asterisk.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="auto_sort">Automatically sorts the pins based on the selected "Sort by" options. </whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="manual_sort">Turns off the automatic "Sort by" options and enables you to drag selected pins to adjust the pin order. Select the desired pin types from the upper right pane, and then click Manual Sort. Afterwards, click a pin to select it, and then drag it to the desired position.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="alphanumeric">Sorts the list of available signals in alphanumeric order.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="bus_element_order">Sorts the list of available signals in the order of bus elements.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="ascending">Sorts the list of available signals in ascending alphanumeric or bus element order.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="descending">Sorts the list of available signals in descending alphanumeric or bus element order.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="assign_signals">
Assigns the selected signals, those in bold type, to the list of pins.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="check_signals">
Checks the validity of the sequence of selected signals and corresponding pins. If the selected signal and the sequence following it in the right pane cannot be used for the selected pin and the sequence following it in the left pane, the software generates a message for each invalid assignment.</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
    <dialog name="back_annotate" href="/index.htm#context/user/backannotating_assignments">
      <whatsthis name="io_place">Writes the I/O LOCATE preferences generated by PAR to the .lpf file.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="io_config">Writes the IOBUF preferences generated by PAR to the .lpf file.</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
    <dialog name="block" href="/index.htm#context/user/setting_block_preference">
      <whatsthis name="block_buses">Blocks the selected bus and all paths through it.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="available_buses">Lists all available buses.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="bus_filter">Enables you to create a single BLOCK preference for multiple buses. Using wildcard notation, type a string (case-sensitive) to narrow the list to the buses you want to include.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="from_asics_pin">Lists the pins of the selected ASIC. Select the source pin for the ASIC you want to block.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="from_asics_pin_filter">Allows you to narrow the list of ASIC pins displayed.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="to_asics_pin">Lists the pins of the selected ASIC. Select the destination pin for the ASIC you want to block.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="to_asics_pin_filter">Allows you to narrow the list of ASIC pins displayed.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="block_nets">Blocks the selected net and all paths through it.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="block_paths_for">Blocks the path from one selected group or object to another.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="available_nets">
Lists all available nets.
      </whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="net_filter">Enables you to create a single BLOCK preference for multiple nets. Using wildcard notation, type a string (case-sensitive) to narrow the list to the nets you want to include. </whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="from_user_groups">Lists the defined port, cell, and ASIC groups in your design. Select the source group for the path you want to block.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="from_group_filter">Allows you to narrow the list of groups displayed.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="to_user_groups">
Lists the defined port, cell, and ASIC groups in your design. Select the destination group for the path you want to block.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="to_group_filter">Allows you to narrow the list of groups displayed.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="from_clock_nets">Lists the clock nets in the design. Select the source net for the path you want to block.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="from_clock_nets_filter">Allows you to narrow the list of clock nets displayed.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="to_clock_nets">Lists the clock nets in the design. Select the destination net for the path you want to block.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="to_clock_nets_filter">Allows you to narrow the list of clock nets displayed.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="from_ports">Lists the ports in the design. Select the source port for the path you want to block.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="from_ports_filter">Allows you to narrow the list of ports displayed.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="to_ports">Lists the ports in the design. Select the destination port for the path you want to block.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="to_ports_filter">Allows you to narrow the list of ports displayed.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="from_cells">Lists the cells in the design. Select the source cell for the path you want to block.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="from_cells_filter">Allows you to narrow the list of cells displayed.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="to_cells">Lists the cells in the design. Select the destination cell for the path you want to block.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="to_cells_filter">Allows you to narrow the list of cells displayed.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="from_asics">Lists the ASICs in the design. Select the source ASIC for the path you want to block.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="from_asics_filter">Allows you to narrow the list of ASICs displayed.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="to_asics">Lists the ASICs in the design. Select the destination ASIC for the path you want to block.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="to_asics_filter">Allows you to narrow the list of ASICs displayed.</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
    <dialog name="clkregion" href="/index.htm#context/user/defining_a_clock_region">
      <whatsthis name="region_name">Specifies a unique name to identify the clock region.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="prohibit">Reserves the area defined by the clock region and prevents it from being used in the next placement process.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="anchor">Identifies the upper left corner of the bounding box that will define the clock region.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="bbox">Sets the height and width of the clock region's bounding box.</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
    <dialog name="clkskewdiff" href="/index.htm#context/user/setting_clkskewdiff_preference">
      <whatsthis name="available_clock_nets_ports_1">Lists the available input clock ports.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="available_clock_nets_ports_2">Lists the available input clock ports.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="max_time_unit">Specifies the maximum skew between the selected clock ports.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="min_time_unit">Specifies the minimum skew between the selected clock ports.</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
    <dialog name="freq" href="/index.htm#context/user/setting_period_pref">
      <whatsthis name="type_period">Creates a period preference for verifying sequential data paths in the design.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="type_frequency">Creates a frequency preference for establishing minimum operating frequency.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="none_second_type">Applies the clock preference to all sequential input pins that do not have a specific clock period/frequency.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="clock_net_second_type">Applies the preference to all sequential output to sequential input pins clocked by a specified net.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="clock_port_second_type">Applies the preference to the specified top-level clock signal port.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="available_clock_nets_ports">
Lists all available nets or clock ports in your design, depending on the selection you made under Second Type. </whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="filter">For nets, enables you to create a single PERIOD or FREQUENCY preference for multiple clock nets. Using wildcard notation, type a string (case-sensitive) to limit the list to the desired clock nets. For ports, the filter narrows the list of ports displayed. You must then select a clock port from the list.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="time_frequency">
Specify a time value in ns or a frequency value in MHz.
      </whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="hold_margin">
Adds a specified hold time margin per clock domain to avoid possible hold time violations based on design constraints.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="par_adj">
Enables you to loosen requirements for place-and-route results while tightening up requirements reported by TRACE. Specify any positive value. Example: if FREQUENCY is set to 250MHz, and PAR_ADJ to 20, the software will use 270MHz to direct PAR, while running TRACE on 250MHz.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="clock_jitter">Type a value in nanoseconds for peak-to-peak jitter on the incoming clock. Trace will use half of this peak-to-peak jitter value for all analysis.</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
    <dialog name="group" href="/index.htm#context/user/defining_groups_for_cell_port_and_asic">
      <whatsthis name="group_name">
Specifies the name of the cell, port, or ASIC group. </whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="by">
Lists the methods for selecting cell instances or ports, which help you narrow down your choices in the Available Instances/Ports list for Cell and Port types.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="left_pane_list">For Cell, displays available clocks, clock enables, sync or async resets, depending on your selection from the "By" menu. For ASICs, displays available ASIC instances.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="middle_pane_list">
Lists the available instances, ports, or pins, based on type of group and the selection you have made from the "By" menu and the left-hand list.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="selected_list">
Lists the selected instances, ports, or ASIC-pin pairs, based on the group type you have selected. These will become members of the current group when you click the Add button.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="filter_left_pane">Limits the objects displayed in the list. Type a string (case-sensitive) using the characters you want to include, and click Go. To recover the original list, delete the string in the edit box and click Go.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="filter_middle_pane">Limits the objects displayed in the list. Type a string (case-sensitive) using the characters you want to include, and click Go. To recover the original list, delete the string in the edit box and click Go.</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
    <dialog name="gsrnet" href="/index.htm#context/user/set_global_set_reset_net_preference">
      <whatsthis name="Available_Logical_Nets">Displays the available nets in the design. Click the &gt; button to add one or more selected nets to the Selected Logical Nets list.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="filter">Enables you to use wildcards to narrow the list of available logical nets.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="Selected_Logical_Nets">Displays the nets you have selected from the Available Logical Nets list. A GSR_NET preference will be created for each net in this list.</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
    <dialog name="ioclk" href="/index.htm#context/user/setting_input_setup_clock_to_out_preference">
      <whatsthis name="input_setup_type">
Establishes the setup time requirement for input ports relative to the clock net. </whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="clock_to_out_type">Establishes the maximum allowable output delay relative to clock. </whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="all_ports_second_type">Sets the time delay from all ports to the specified clock port/net.    </whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="individual_ports_second_type">Sets the time delay from the specified port to the specified clock port/net.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="group_second_type">Sets the time delay from the specified group to the specified clock port/net. </whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="available_list">
Lists all available ports or groups.      </whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="available_list_filter">Limits the objects displayed in the list. For ports, you can use wildcards to create a single preference for multiple ports. For groups, you can limit the list of groups displayed, and then select a group from the list. To recover the original list, delete the string in the edit box and click Go.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="available_clock_ports_nets">
Lists all available clock ports/nets in your design.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="clock_ports_nets_list_filter">Limits the objects displayed in the list. Type a string (case-sensitive) using the characters you want to include, and click Go. To recover the original list, delete the string in the edit box and click Go.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="input_delay">
For INPUT_SETUP, treats the value in the Time box as an input delay value.      </whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="output_delay">
For CLOCK_TO_OUT, treats the value in the Time box as an output delay value.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="pll_phase_back">
Reverses the offset direction of the phase delay programmed into a PLL.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="ss">Indicates that the data input and clock input are source-synchronous. This will allow input jitter specified on the clock to be ignored for setup and hold timing analysis.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="clock_out_ports">
Enables you to select the output clock port with respect to the data delay that needs to be measured. </whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="clock_out_ports_filter">Limits the objects displayed in the list. Type of string (case-sensitive)using the characters you want to include and click Go. To recover the original list, delete the string in the edit box and click Go.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="time">
Sets the maximum delay value.
      </whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="hold_time">
Sets the hold time for INPUT_SETUP.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="min_time">Sets the minimum time for CLOCK_TO_OUT.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="clock_offset">
Adjusts the timing analysis by a multiple of the clock period. The path timing will be adjusted by &lt;n&gt;*clock_period, where &lt;n&gt; is a floating point number and can be negative.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="from_cell">
For CLOCK_TO_OUT, opens the "From Cell" dialog box, enabling you to specify a cell as the starting point.</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
    <dialog name="maxdelay" href="/index.htm#context/user/setting_maxdelay_preference">
      <whatsthis name="from">Sets the start point component.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="to">Sets the end point component.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="time">Sets the delay value.</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
    <dialog name="maxdelay_net" href="/index.htm#context/user/setting_maxdelay_preference_for_net">
      <whatsthis name="datapath">When set to ON,includes only data path delay information.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="delay">Sets the maximum delay value for the net.</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
    <dialog name="multicycle" href="/index.htm#context/user/setting_multicycle_preference">
      <whatsthis name="general">
Relaxes the PERIOD or FREQUENCY preferences on the specified general path.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="clock_net_to_clock_net">Relaxes the PERIOD or FREQUENCY preferences on a path starting from one clock net to another.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="slow_fast_path_exception">Relaxes the PERIOD or FREQUENCY preferences on a path starting from one user group to another.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="from">
Sets the start point component.    </whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="to">
Sets the end point component.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="time_x">
Sets the delay value for the MULTICYCLE path. X specifies the multiple of the clock period for the clock driving the start and end point components.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="path_type">Specifies the path type. READPATHS defines the paths at memory-block read-side. SAMECLKEN define the paths at the source/destination register controlled by the same clock-enable signal. CLKEN_NET defines the paths at the source/destination register controlled by a given net.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="clk_en_net">Specifies the net name for CLKEN_NET.</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
    <dialog name="pin_csv" href="/index.htm#context/user/export_pin_layout_file">
      <whatsthis name="pin_field">Select the items from the list that you want to appear as column headings in the file.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="separator">Select a delimiter that is used to separate the data into columns.</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
    <dialog name="pin_migration" href="/index.htm#context/user/selecting_device_for_pin_migration">
      <whatsthis name="device_list">Lists the devices that are compatible with the current device. Select the desired devices for possible pin migration. Incompatible pins will be highlighted in Spreadsheet View and Package View.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="disable_assign">Prevents assignments to any pins that are incompatible with the devices you have selected.</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
    <dialog name="region" href="/index.htm#context/user/setting_regions">
      <whatsthis name="region_name">Specifies a unique name to identify the region.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="anchor">Identifies the upper left corner of the bounding box that will define the region.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="bbox">Sets the height and width of the region's bounding box.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="prohibit">Reserves the area defined by the region and prevents it from being used in the next placement process.</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
    <dialog name="ugroup" href="/index.htm#context/user/creating_ugroups">
      <whatsthis name="ugroup_name">Specifies a unique name to identify the UGROUP.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="anchor">Enables you set a site or region in the device resource area as an anchor location for the UGROUP.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="region">Anchors the UGROUP as a floating group inside an established region. Choose the region from the drop-down menu.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="site">Specifies the upper left row and column of a rectangular shape that will anchor the UGROUP in the device resource area.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="bbox">Enables you to set the bounding box for the UGROUP.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="height">Sets the height of the UGROUP's bounding box in the device resource area.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="width">Sets the width of the UGROUP's bounding box in the device resource area.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="available_instances">Displays a list of logical instances. Select the instances that you want to include in the UGROUP and click &gt; to move them to the "Selected Instances" list.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="filter">Enables you to limit the list of available instances by using a string (case-sensitive) and wildcard notation. Type a string in the text box and click Go.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="selected_instances">Displays a list of logical instances that you have selected to be included in the UGROUP. To remove selected instances from the list, click the &lt; button.</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
    <dialog name="vrefloc" href="/index.htm#context/user/setting_vref_locations">
      <whatsthis name="vref_name">Specify a unique name to identify the vref location.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="site">Lists all the designated VREF pins on the target device and shows the bank for each. Select one from the list to locate the VREF.</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
    <dialog name="options">
      <whatsthis name="color">Defines the font color scheme for spreadsheets.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="font">Defines the font style and size for spreadsheets.</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
  </tool>
</helpIndex>