<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<helpIndex version="1.0">
  <tool name="NCD_EDITOR" href="/index.htm#context/user/applying_ecos">
    <view name="sysio" href="/index.htm#context/user/editing_sysio_preferences"></view>
    <view name="pll" href="/index.htm#context/user/editing_pll_preferences"></view>
    <view name="memory_initialization" href="/index.htm#context/user/setting_memory_initialization_values"></view>
    <view name="ncd_change_log" href="/index.htm#context/user/tracking_ncd_changes"></view>
    <dialog name="sort" href="/index.htm#context/user/sorting_a_preference_list">
      <whatsthis name="sort_by">Allows you to select the first column to sort by.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Click &lt;b&gt;Ascending&lt;/b&gt; to sort the lowest number, or the beginning of the alphabet first in the sorted list. Blank cells are always sorted first.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Click &lt;b&gt;Descending&lt;/b&gt; to sort the highest number, or the end of the alphabet first in the sorted list. Blank cells are always sorted last.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="then_by">Use these boxes if you are sorting by more than one column. After the list is sorted by the column specified in the Sort By box, the list is sorted by additional columns in sequence.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Click &lt;b&gt;Ascending&lt;/b&gt; to sort the lowest number, or the beginning of the alphabet first in the sorted list. Blank cells are always sorted first.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Click &lt;b&gt;Descending&lt;/b&gt; to sort the highest number, or the end of the alphabet first in the sorted list. Blank cells are always sorted last.</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
    <dialog name="update_initial_memory" href="/index.htm#context/user/updating_initial_values">
      <whatsthis name="file_format">Specifies the format of the memory initialization (.mem) file.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="init_all_1s">Fills the EBR memory with all 1s instead of using the values in the .mem file.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="init_all_0s">Fills the EBR memory with all 0s instead of using the values in the .mem file.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="memory_file">Specifies the memory initialization (.mem) file for the selected memory block. Click the ... button to browse to the file. The .mem file contains initial values for memory components such as RAM and ROM blocks.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="lpc_file">Specifies the Lattice Semiconductor parameter configuration (.lpc) file, which contains the configuration parameters that you selected in IPexpress. This box automatically specifies the .lpc file included in the current design directory. If your .lpc file is stored outside the design directory, click the ... button to browse to the file.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="depth_width_mode">Displays the memory parameters contained in the .lpc file.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="components_list">Lists all the memory module components in the selected memory block and their placement information.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="update_btn">Updates the current memory block's initial memory values. A message will appear telling you whether the initialization succeeds or not.</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
    <dialog name="update_ufm_parameters" href="/index.htm#context/user/updating_initial_values_ufm">
      <whatsthis name="init_all_zeroes">Enabled - Initializes the memory with all zeros. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Disabled - Initializes the memory with the memory initialization (.mem) file that you specify in the UFM Initialization Data File box.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="file_format">Specifies the format of the memory initialization (.mem) file that you specify in the UFM Initialization Data File box.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="file_name">Specifies the memory initialization (.mem) file for initializing the UFM. Click the ... button to browse to the file.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
The default place where Lattice Diamond searches for the UFM initialization file is the project implementation directory. If the initialization file you specify is not in the implementation directory, ECO Editor will copy it to the implementation directory and inform you the file is copied.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="pages_start_page">Occupied UFM Pages - Shows the size of the memory in pages with 128 bits/page. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Initialization Data Starts at Page - Shows the page that the initialization data will start at. This location depends on the Occupied UFM Pages and the size of the flash memory available in the selected device.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="update_btn">Updates the UFM's initial memory values. A message will appear telling you whether the initialization succeeds or not.</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
  </tool>
</helpIndex>