<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<helpIndex version="1.0">
  <tool name="Reveal_Inserter" href="/index.htm#context/user/creating_Reveal_modules">
    <view name="design_tree" href="/index.htm#context/user/viewing_signals" />
    <view name="dataset" href="/index.htm#context/user/managing_the_cores" />
    <view name="trigger_output" href="/index.htm#context/user/Trigger_Output_view" />
    <view name="tracesetup" href="/index.htm#context/user/set_up_trace_signals" />
    <view name="triggersetup" href="/index.htm#context/user/setting_trigger_signals" />

    <dialog name="Insert_Debug_to_Design" href="/index.htm#context/user/Inserting_debug_cores">
      <whatsthis name="Import_Reveal_file">
Imports the .rvl file into the design project. Importing the .rvl file is required to add the modules to the design.
      </whatsthis>
    </dialog>

    <dialog name="Select_Signals_dialog" href="/index.htm#context/user/Selecting_Trigger_Signals">
      <whatsthis name="Select_Signals">
Displays the signals available for trigger units.
      </whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="Selected_Signals">
Displays the signals that you have selected to include in the trigger unit. You can select up to 256 signals.
      </whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="right">
Moves selected signals from the left pane to the right pane.
      </whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="left">
Moves selected signals from the right pane to the left pane.
      </whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="up_arrow">
Moves the selected signal up one line. The order of the signals affects how the comparison is performed.
      </whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="down_arrow">
Moves the selected signal down one line. The order of the signals affects how the comparison is performed.
      </whatsthis>
    </dialog>

    <dialog name="Token_Manager" href="/index.htm#context/user/creating_a_token_set">
      <whatsthis name="Token_Sets"><![CDATA[
Lists all the token sets in the Reveal project.
<br>
Name: Specifies the name of the token set.
<br>
Max Token Bits: Specifies the maximum bit size of the token value in the token set.
      ]]></whatsthis>

      <whatsthis name="add_set">
Adds a new token set to the list.
      </whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="remove_set">
Removes the selected token set.
      </whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="Tokens_in_token_set"><![CDATA[
Defines the tokens in the selected token set. You can edit the names and values of tokens directly in the table cell.
<br>
Name: Specifies the name of the token. This is the label that will appear in the Waveform View tab of Reveal Analyzer.
<br>
Value: Specifies the bus value the token represents.
      ]]></whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="add_token">
Adds a new token.
      </whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="remove_token">
Removes the selected token.
      </whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="Import">
Opens a previously created token (.rvt) file, and adds the file's token sets into the Reveal project.
      </whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="Export">
Saves the token sets into a separate token (.rvt) file. The .rvt file can be used in other Reveal projects.
      </whatsthis>
    </dialog>

    <dialog name="Search_Result" href="/index.htm#context/user/searching_signals">
      <whatsthis name="Select_Search_Signals">
Displays the signals that the search found. Select the signals you want to use.
      </whatsthis>
    </dialog>
  </tool>
</helpIndex>