<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<helpIndex version="1.0">
  <tool name="strategy" href="/index.htm#context/user/using_strategies">
    <dialog name="properties_setting" href="/index.htm#context/user/using_strategies">
      <whatsthis name="process_list">Lists major processes involved in the current design flow.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="setting_list">Lists all the settings associated with the selected process.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="display_catalog">Filters the settings displayed for the selected process.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="default_btn">Specifies all the settings for the currently selected process to their default values.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="tip_box">Displays brief definition for the highlighted setting.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="ok">Applies and saves any changes you have made and closes this dialog box.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="cancel">Closes this dialog box without saving any changes you have made.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="apply">Applies and saves any changes you have made in this dialog box.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="help">Displays the help contents on this dialog box or detailed description for the highlighted setting.</whatsthis>
      
                  <description name="PROP_SYN_EdfAllowDUPMod" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_allow_duplicate_modules">Allows the use of duplicate modules in your design.</description>
      <description name="PROP_SYN_EdfArea" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_area_for_synplify_pro_">Specifies optimization preference for area reduction over timing delay reduction.</description>
      <description name="PROP_SYN_EdfArrangeVHDLFiles" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_arrange_vhdl_files">Allows Synplify Pro to reorder the VHDL source files for synthesis.</description>
      <description name="PROP_SYN_ClockConversion" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_clock_conversion">Controls gated and generated clock conversion.</description>
      <description name="PROP_SYN_CmdLineArgs" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_command_line_options_for_synplify_pro_">Enables additional command line options for the Synplify Pro Synthesis process.</description>
      <description name="PROP_SYN_EdfDefEnumEncode" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_default_enum_encoding">(For VHDL designs) Defines how enumerated data types are implemented.</description>
      <description name="PROP_SYN_EdfInsertIO" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_disable_io_insertion_for_synplify_pro_">Controls whether the synthesis tool will add I/O buffers into your design.</description>
      <description name="PROP_SYN_DisableRegisterRep" href="/index.htm#context/ref/Disable_Register_Replication">When this option is set in the strategy, the synthesis tool will NOT duplicate the registers while inferring the address pointers for the RAM during Shift-register inference. By default this option is OFF and the tool will duplicate the address pointer registers to get better performance.</description>
      <description name="PROP_SYN_EdifNames" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_edif_names">Controls the format of bus names in the EDIF file. Select Standard to use brackets in the names of bus signals as in "bus[1]", which is the current standard for Synplify Pro. Select Legacy to use the older format as in "bus_1".</description>
      <description name="PROP_SYN_ExportSetting" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_export_setting">Controls whether the strategy settings are exported to Synplify Pro during interactive synthesis (opening Synplify Pro through the Tools menu). After opening Synplify Pro, you can change settings in Synplify Pro's interface. This option has no effect with integrated or stand-alone synthesis.</description>
      <description name="PROP_SYN_EdfFanout" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_fanout_limit">Controls fanout during synthesis. When the specified fanout limit is achieved, logic will be duplicated.</description>
      <description name="PROP_SYN_EdfGSR" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_force_gsr_for_synplify_pro_">Forces Global Set/Reset Pin usage.</description>
      <description name="PROP_SYN_EdfFrequency" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_frequency_for_synplify_pro_">Specifies the global design frequency (in MHz). Nothing in the Value column means "auto" (the default) and Synplify Pro will try to maximize the frequency of the clocks.</description>
      <description name="PROP_SYN_EdfSymFSM" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_fsm_encoding_for_synplify_pro_">Enables or disables the FSM Compiler and controls the use of FSM synthesis for state machines.</description>
      <description name="PROP_SYN_LibPath" href="/index.htm#context/ref/Library_Directories">Specifies all the paths to the directories which contain the Verilog library files to be included in your design for the project. </description>
      <description name="PROP_SYN_EdfNumCritPath" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_number_of_critical_paths_for_synplify_pro_">Specifies the number of critical timing paths to be reported in the timing report. </description>
      <description name="PROP_SYN_EdfNumStartEnd" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_number_of_start_end_points">Specifies the number of start and end points you want the software to report in the critical path section of the timing report.</description>
      <description name="PROP_SYN_EdfOutNetForm" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_output_netlist_format_for_synplify_pro_">Outputs a mapped Verilog or VHDL netlist for post-synthesis simulation. </description>
      <description name="PROP_SYN_EdfRunRetiming" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_pipelining_and_retiming">Enables the pipelining and retiming features to improve design performance.</description>
      <description name="PROP_SYN_EdfPushTirstates" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_push_tristates">When this is set to True, the Synplify Pro compiler pushes tristates through objects such as muxes, registers, latches, buffers, nets, and tristate buffers, and propagates the high impedance state. </description>
      <description name="PROP_SYN_ResolvedMixedDrivers" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_resolved_mixed_drivers">If a net is driven by a VCC or GND and active drivers, setting this option to True (default) will connect the net to the VCC or GND driver.</description>
      <description name="PROP_SYN_EdfResSharing" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_resource_sharing_for_synplify_pro_">When this is set to True (default), the synthesis tool uses resource sharing techniques to optimize area. </description>
      <description name="PROP_SYN_UpdateCompilePtTimData" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_update_compile_point_timing_data">Determines whether (True) or not (False) changes inside a compile point can cause the compile point (or top-level) containing it to change accordingly.</description>
      <description name="PROP_SYN_EdfUnconsClk" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_use_clock_period_for_unconstrained_i_o">Controls whether to forward annotate constraints for I/O ports without explicit user-defined constraints. </description>
      <description name="PROP_SYN_UseLPF" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_output_preference_file_for_synplify_pro_">When this is set to True (default), Synplify Pro creates a preference (.lpf) file based on the Synopsys Design Constraint (.sdc) file. With this .lpf file, the synthesis constraints will also be applied to the Map Design stage of implementation.</description>
      <description name="PROP_SYN_EdfVerilogInput" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_verilog_input">Specifies the Verilog standard used for the project. </description>
      <description name="PROP_SYN_VHDL2008" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_vhdl_2008">When this is set to True, VHDL 2008 is selected as the VHDL standard for the project.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PRE_VSynComArea" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_area_for_precision_">Specifies optimization preference for area reduction over timing delay reduction. </description>
      <description name="PROP_PRE_EdfArrayBoundsCase" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_array_bounds_case">Enables or disables the Precision tool to check array bounds for Verilog input files.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PRE_EdfAutoResOfRam" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_auto_resource_allocation_of_ram">Enables or disables the automatic resource allocation of RAMs.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PRE_CmdLineArgs" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_command_line_options_for_precision_">Enables additional command line options for the Precision Synthesis process.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PRE_VSynGatedClk" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_convert_gated_clock">Controls the gated-clock conversion by Precision RTL Synthesis during the synthesis phase. </description>
      <description name="PROP_PRE_VSynIOPad" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_disable_i_o_insertion_for_precision_">Controls whether the synthesis tool will add I/O buffers into your design.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PRE_VSynGSR" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_force_gsr_for_precision_">Forces Global Set/Reset Pin usage. </description>
      <description name="PROP_PRE_VSynFreq" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_frequency_for_precision_">Specifies the global design frequency (in MHz). </description>
      <description name="PROP_PRE_VSynFSM" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_fsm_encoding_for_precision_">Specifies the encoding style to use with the design.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PRE_EdfFullCase" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_full_case">When set to True, tells Precision that for all case statements throughout your design, all relevant conditions are specified. If the default assignment is not used then this option prevents the inference of latches.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PRE_EdfIgnoreRamRWCol" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_ignore_ram_read_write_collision">Controls whether to ignore RAM read/write collision.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PRE_EdfDSPAcrossHie" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_infer_dsps_across_hierarchy">When this is set to True, Precision Synthesis will optimize pipeline registers across hierarchical boundaries.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PRE_VSyninpd" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_input_delay_ns_">Specifies the global input delay (in ns) for use with the frequency switch.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PRE_VSynCritcal" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_number_of_critical_paths_for_precision_">Specifies the number of critical timing paths to be reported in the timing report.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PRE_VSynTimSum" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_number_of_timing_summary_paths">Specifies the number of timing paths to be reported in the timing report.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PRE_VSynoutd" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_output_delay_ns_">Specifies the global output delay (in ns) for use with the frequency switch.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PRE_VSynOutNetForm" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_output_netlist_format_for_precision_">Outputs a mapped Verilog or VHDL netlist for post-synthesis simulation.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PRE_VSynOutPref" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_output_preference_file_for_precision">When this is set to True (default), Precision RTL Synthesis creates a preference file and gives it the same name as the module: module_name.prf.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PRE_EdfParaCase" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_parallel_case">When set to True, tells Precision that for all case statements throughout your design, case conditions are mutually exclusive. This results in a multiplexer implementation instead of a priority encoder.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PRE_EdfReencodeFSM" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_reencode_fsm_outputs">Controls Precision FSM extraction and re-encoding when Precision needs to create decoding logic. </description>
      <description name="PROP_PRE_VSynRepClkFreq" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_report_clock_frequencies">Setting this to True (default) lets the software report all clock frequencies.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PRE_EdfMissConstraint" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_report_missing_constraints">When this is set to True, the timing report will report missing constraints.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PRE_EdfTimingViolation" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_report_timing_violations">When this is set to True (default), the timing report will include timing violations.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PRE_EdfResSharing" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_resource_sharing_for_precision_">When this is set to True (default), the synthesis tool uses resource sharing techniques to optimize area.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PRE_VSynRetime" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_run_retiming">Setting this to True (default) causes the advanced retiming algorithms to be run.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PRE_EdfClockDomainCross" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_show_clock_domain_crossing">When this is set to True, the timing report will show clock domain crossings.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PRE_EdfNetFanout" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_show_net_fanout">When this is set to True (default), the timing report will show net fanout.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PRE_VSynTransform" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_transform_set_reset_on_dffs_to_latches">Setting this to True transforms Set/Reset on DFFs to Latches.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PRE_EdfUseSafeFSM" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_use_safe_fsm">Enables or disables the use of safe FSMs.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PRE_EdfVlog2001" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_verilog_standard_v2001">When this is set to True, Verilog 2001 is selected as the Verilog standard for the project. Otherwise, Verilog 95 will be used.</description>
      <description name="PROP_LST_AllowDUPMod" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_allow_dup_modules">When set to True, allows the design to keep duplicate modules. LSE issues a warning and uses the last definition of the module. Any previous definitions are ignored. The default is False, which causes an error if there are duplicate modules.</description>
      <description name="PROP_LST_CarryChainLength" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_carry_chain_length">Specifies the maximum number of carry chain cells (CCUs) that get mapped to a single carry chain. Default is 0, which is interpreted as infinite length.</description>
      <description name="PROP_LST_CmdLineArgs" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_command_line_options_for_lse_">Enables additional command line options for the LSE Synthesis process.</description>
      <description name="PROP_LST_DecodeUnreachableStates" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_decode_unreachable_states">When set to True, synthesis infers safe recovery logic from unreachable states in all the state machines of the design.</description>
      <description name="PROP_LST_DisableDistRam" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_DisableDistRAM">When set to True, inferred memory will not use the distributed RAM of the PFUs.</description>
      <description name="PROP_LST_DSPStyle" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_dsp_style">Specifies how DSP modules should be implemented: with DSP resources or with Logic (LUTs).</description>
      <description name="PROP_LST_DSPUtil" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_dsp_utilization">Specifies the percentage of DSP sites that LSE should try to use.</description>
      <description name="PROP_LST_EBRUtil" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_ebr_utilization">Specifies EBR utilization target setting in percent of total vacant sites. LSE will honor the setting and do the resource computation accordingly. Default is 100 (in percentage).</description>
      <description name="PROP_LST_FIXGATEDCLKS" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_fix_gated_clocks">When set to True, LSE changes standard gated clocks to forms more effective for FPGAs. Clocks are gated with AND or OR gates to conserve power, but in FPGAs such clocks cause skew and prevent global clock resources from being used. The Fix Gated Clocks option is ignored if the Optimization Goal option is set to Area.</description>
      <description name="PROP_LST_ForceGSRInfer" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_force_gsr_for_lse_">Enables (True) or disables (False) forced use of the global set/reset routing resources. When the value is Auto, the synthesis tool decides whether to use the global set/reset resources.</description>
      <description name="PROP_LST_FSMEncodeStyle" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_fsm_encoding_style">Specifies the encoding style to use with the design.</description>
      <description name="PROP_LST_EdfHardtimer" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_hardware_evaluation_for_lse_">Enables or disables the ability to temporarily test IP in a device without an IP license. If enabled, a timer is added to the design that allows unlicensed IP to function for about 4 hours in a device. If disabled, you cannot generate a bitstream if there are any unlicensed IP in the design.</description>
      <description name="PROP_LST_InterFileDump" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_intermediate_file_dump">If you set this to True, LSE will produce intermediate encrypted Verilog files. If you supply Lattice with these files, they can be decrypted and analyzed for problems. This option is good for analyzing simulation issues.</description>
      <description name="PROP_LST_LoopLimit" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_loop_limit">Specifies the maximum number of iterations of "for" and "while" loops in the source code. The limit is applied when the loop index is a variable, not when it is a constant. The higher the loop_limit, the longer the run time. The default value is 1950. Setting a higher value may cause stack overflow during some of the optimizations during synthesis. A lower value will be ignored and the default used instead.</description>
      <description name="PROP_LST_EdfInLibPath" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_macro_search_path_for_lse_">Allows you to specify a path (or paths) to locate physical macro files used in a given design. The software will add the specified paths to the list of directories to search when resolving file references. The option can also be used for indicating the directories containing include files that are specified in the RTL design files.</description>
      <description name="PROP_LST_MaxFanout" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_max_fanout_limit">Specifies the maximum fanout setting. LSE will make sure that any net in the design is not exceeding this limit. Default is 1000 fanouts.</description>
      <description name="PROP_LST_EdfMemPath" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_memory_initial_value_file_search_path_for_lse_">Allows you to specify a path (or paths) to locate memory initialization file (.mem) used in a given design. The software will add the specified path(s) to the list of directories to search when resolving file references.</description>
      <description name="PROP_LST_MuxStyle" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_max_style">Specifies the MUX style setting, which controls the way the macrogenerator implements the multiplexer macros.</description>
      <description name="PROP_LST_NumCriticalPaths" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_number_of_critical_paths_for_lse_">Specifies the number of critical timing paths to be reported in the timing report.</description>
      <description name="PROP_LST_OptimizeGoal" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_optimization_goal">Enables LSE to optimize the design for area, speed, or balanced.</description>
      <description name="PROP_LST_PropagatConst" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_propagate_constants">When set to True (default), enables constant propagation to reduce area, where possible. LSE will then eliminate the logic used when constant inputs to logic cause their outputs to be constant. </description>
      <description name="PROP_LST_RAMStyle" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_ram_style">Sets the type of random access memory globally to distributed, embedded block RAM, or registers.</description>
      <description name="PROP_LST_RemoveDupRegs" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_remove_duplicate_registers">Specifies the removal of duplicate registers.</description>
      <description name="PROP_LST_EdfInRemLoc" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_remove_loc_properties_for_lse_">Setting this to On removes LOC properties in the synthesized design before building the Native Generic Database (.ngd) file.</description>
      <description name="PROP_LST_ResolvedMixedDrivers" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_resolved_mixed_drivers_LSE">If a net is driven by a VCC or GND and active drivers, setting this option to True connects the net to the VCC or GND driver.</description>
      <description name="PROP_LST_ResourceShare" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_resource_sharing_for_lse_">When this is set to True (default), the synthesis tool uses resource sharing techniques to optimize area. </description>
      <description name="PROP_LST_ROMStyle" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_rom_style">Allows you to globally implement ROM architectures using dedicated, distributed ROM, or a combination of the two (Auto).</description>
      <description name="PROP_LST_EdfFrequency" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_target_frequency">Specifies the target frequency setting. This frequency applies to all the clocks in the design. If there are some clocks defined in an .ldc file, the remaining clocks will get this frequency setting. When a create_clock constraint is available in an .ldc file, LSE ignores the Target Frequency setting for that clock and uses the value from the create_clock constraint instead.</description>
      <description name="PROP_LST_CarryChain" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_use_carry_chain">Turns on (True) or off (False) carry chain implementation for adders. Default is True.</description>
      <description name="PROP_LST_IOInsertion" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_use_io_insertion">When set to True, LSE uses I/O insertion and GSR.</description>
      <description name="PROP_LST_UseIOReg" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_use_io_registers">When True, this option forces the synthesis tool to pack all input and output registers into I/O pad cells based on the timing requirements for the target device family. Auto, the default setting, enables this register packing if Optimization Goal is set to Area. If Optimization Goal is Timing or Balanced, Auto disables register packing.</description>
      <description name="PROP_LST_UseLPF" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_output_preference_file_for_lse_">LSE creates a preference (.lpf) file based on the Synopsys Design Constraint (.sdc) file. (When you use LSE, SDC constraints must be in a Lattice Design Constraints (.ldc) file.) When this option is set to True, the synthesis constraints are also applied to the Map Design stage of implementation.</description>
      <description name="PROP_LST_VHDL2008" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_VHDL2008_lse">When this is set to True, VHDL 2008 is selected as the VHDL standard for the project.</description>
      <description name="PROP_BD_CmdLineArgs" href="/index.htm#context/ref/command_line_options_synplify_translate_design">Enables EDIF2NGD command line options for the Synplify Translate Design process.</description>
      <description name="PROP_BD_EdfInBusNameConv" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_consistent_bus_name_conversion">Allows you to set preferences for bus signals in Verilog and VHDL designs that can be honored by LSE, Synopsys Synplify Pro, and Mentor Graphics Precision synthesis tools.</description>
      <description name="PROP_BD_EdfHardtimer" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_hardware_evaluation_for_translate_design_">Enables or disables the ability to temporarily test IP in a device without an IP license. If enabled, a timer is added to the design that allows unlicensed IP to function for about 4 hours in a device. If disabled, you cannot generate a bitstream if there are any unlicensed IP in the design.</description>
      <description name="PROP_BD_EdfInLibPath" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_macro_search_path_for_translate_design_">Allows you to specify a path (or paths) to locate physical macro files used in a given design. The software will add the specified paths to the list of directories to search when resolving file references.</description>
      <description name="PROP_BD_EdfMemPath" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_memory_initial_value_file_search_path_for_translate_design_">Allows you to specify paths to locate memory initialization files (.mem) used in a given design. Diamond will add the specified paths to the list of directories to search when resolving file references.</description>
      <description name="PROP_BD_ParSearchPath" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_partition_search_path_for_translate_design">Allows you to specify paths to locate native generic object files (.ngo) that define partitions used in the design. Diamond will add the specified paths to the list of directories to search when resolving file references. The partition .ngo files will be loaded and used for replacing the original partition.</description>
      <description name="PROP_BD_EdfInRemLoc" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_remove_loc_properties_for_translate_design_">Setting this to On removes LOC properties in the synthesized design before building the Native Generic Database (.ngd) file.</description>
      <description name="PROP_MAP_MapModArgs" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_command_line_options_for_map_design_">Enables additional command line options for the associated process.</description>
      <description name="PROP_MAP_IgnorePreErr" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_ignore_preference_errors_for_map_design_">Enables or disables the Map Design process to ignore errors in the preference file.</description>
      <description name="PROP_MAP_MAPInferGSR" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_infer_gsr">Enables or disables the GSR inferencing.</description>
      <description name="PROP_MAP_MAPIORegister" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_io_registering">Directs the I/O register packing.</description>
      <description name="PROP_MAP_OvermapDevice" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_overmap_device_if_design_does_not_fit">When this is set to True, the Map Design process will write a Native Circuit Description (.ncd) file even if the device is too small for the design. This .ncd file cannot be used for Place and Route Design, just for you to observe mapping results.</description>
      <description name="PROP_MAP_PackLogMapDes" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_pack_logic_block_util_blank_or_0_to_100_">Sets the relative density (of available slices) at which the slices within a device are to be packed, in terms of a percentage of the available slices in the device.</description>
      <description name="PROP_MAP_RegRetiming" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_register_retiming">Moves registers across combinational logic to balance timing according to the constraints tSU (INPUT_SETUP), tCO (CLOCK_TO_OUT), and fMAX (FREQUENCY).</description>
      <description name="PROP_MAP_SigCrossRef" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_report_signal_cross_reference">When this is set to True, the map report (.mrp) will show where nets in the logical design were mapped in the physical design (NCD).</description>
      <description name="PROP_MAP_SymCrossRef" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_report_symbol_cross_reference">When this is set to True, the map report (.mrp) will show where symbols in the logical design were mapped in the physical design (NCD).</description>
      <description name="PROP_MAP_TimingDriven" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_timing_driven_mapping">Allows you to apply timing-driven logic collapsing and optimization to further optimize the critical paths.</description>
      <description name="PROP_MAP_TimingDrivenNodeRep" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_timing_driven_node_replication">Allows you to activate timing driven logic replication.</description>
      <description name="PROP_MAP_TimingDrivenPack" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_timing_driven_packing">Allows you to activate timing driven packing of LUT/FF, FF/LUT, and LUT/LUT in the same slice.</description>
      <description name="PROP_MAPSTA_AnalysisOption" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_analysis_options_for_map_trace_">Specifies the analysis type.</description>
      <description name="PROP_MAPSTA_AutoTiming" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_auto_timing_for_map_trace_">Lists the auto-generated timing preferences in the TRACE report.</description>
      <description name="PROP_MAPSTA_CheckUnconstrainedConns" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_check_unconstrained_connections_for_map_trace_">Reports connections not covered by a timing preference.</description>
      <description name="PROP_MAPSTA_CheckUnconstrainedPaths" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_check_unconstrained_paths_for_map_trace_">Reports paths not covered by a timing preference.</description>
      <description name="PROP_MAPSTA_FullName" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_full_name_for_map_trace_">When this is set to True, the TRACE report will show full-length component names instead of the truncated names.</description>
      <description name="PROP_MAPSTA_NumUnconstrainedPaths" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_number_unconstrained_paths_for_map_trace_">Sets the maximum number of unconstrained paths that will be reported. "Unconstrained paths" are those not covered by a timing preference.</description>
      <description name="PROP_MAPSTA_RptAsynTimLoop" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_report_asynchronous_timing_loops_for_map_trace_">Produces a report of paths that could not be analyzed because they are asynchronous loop.</description>
      <description name="PROP_MAPSTA_ReportStyle" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_report_style_for_map_trace_">Specifies the type of the timing report.</description>
      <description name="PROP_MAPSTA_RouteEstAlogtithm" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_route_estimation_algorithm_">Configures the route estimation algorithm for pre-route static timing analysis.</description>
      <description name="PROP_MAPSTA_WordCasePaths" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_worst_case_paths_0_4096_for_map_trace_">Specifies the number of paths to be reported for each timing preference. Enter zero or a grater value.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PAR_parHold" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_auto_hold_time_correction">Controls whether the router will automatically insert extra wires to compensate for hold-time violations on affected registers. Auto hold-time correction has a negative impact on your setup time. If the setup time is more design critical, turn off this option. The default is On.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PAR_PARClockSkew" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_clock_skew_minimization">Balances routing to reduce skews for clock signals that are not assigned to the global clock tree.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PAR_PARModArgs" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_command_line_options_for_place_route_design_">Allows you to specify options from the par command without directly using the command line. Type in a string of options without the par command. For example: -exp parPathBased=ON:parHold=1</description>
      <description name="PROP_PAR_RoutingCDP" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_congestion_driven_placement">Enables or disables the congestion-driven placement algorithm. </description>
      <description name="PROP_PAR_RoutingCDR" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_congestion_driven_routing">Enables or disables the congestion-driven routing algorithm. </description>
      <description name="PROP_PAR_CrDlyStFileParDes" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_create_delay_statistic_file">When set to True, outputs a delay report file (.dly) on each PAR run.</description>
      <description name="PROP_THERMAL_DefaultFreq" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_default_clock_frequency">(MachXO3L/LF 9400C/E devices only.) The proper Default Clock Frequency (MHz) must be set before running the Thermal Analysis process. Default setting of 0 will cause an error.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PAR_DisableTDParDes" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_disable_timing_driven">Enables or disables the timing-driven option for the PAR run.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PAR_RunParWithTrce" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_generate_trace_report_for_each_iteration">Generates a post-PAR TRACE report (.twr) for each intermediate NCD created by multi-PAR.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PAR_PrefErrorOut" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_ignore_preference_errors_for_place_route_design_">Enables or disables the Place and Route Design process to ignore errors in the preference file. </description>
      <description name="PROP_PAR_ParMultiNodeList" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_multi_tasking_node_list">Allows you to specify the node file name for the multi-tasking PAR.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PAR_parPathBased" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_path_based_placement">Allows you to apply path-based placement. Path-based placement gives better performance and more predictable results.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PAR_EffortParDes" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_placement_effort_level">Specifies the effort level of the design from 1 (simplest designs) to 5 (most complex designs).</description>
      <description name="PROP_PAR_PlcStCostTblParDes" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_placement_iteration_start_pt">Specifies the cost table to use (from 1-100) to begin the PAR run.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PAR_PlcIterParDes" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_placement_iterations_0_99_0_run_until_solved_">Specifies the maximum number of placement/routing passes (0-100, 0 = run until solved) to be run (regardless of whether they complete) at the Placement Effort Level.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PAR_SaveBestRsltParDes" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_placement_save_best_run">Determines the number (1-100) of best outputs of the Place and Route run to save (defaults to 1). </description>
      <description name="PROP_PAR_MultiSeedSortMode" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_placement_sort_best_run">Specifies how to sort the results of the Place and Route run in the PAR report. Results are sorted first by the number of unrouted connections. Then the results are ranked by timing. Choose whether you want to use the worst-slack value or the timing score to rank the results.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PAR_RemoveDir" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_remove_previous_design_directory">When this is set to True (default), the software removes the contents of the project design directory before Place and Route Design is rerun.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PAR_RouteDlyRedParDes" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_routing_delay_reduction_passes">Determines the number of passes to be run for Routing Delay Reduction and Routing Resource Optimization properties. The first delay-based cleanup pass produces the greatest improvement.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PAR_NewRouteParDes" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_routing_method">Specifies router algorithm.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PAR_RoutePassParDes" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_routing_passes">Determines the maximum number of routing passes the place and route tool takes.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PAR_RouteResOptParDes" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_routing_resource_optimization">Determines the number of cost-based cleanup passes to run.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PAR_ParRunPlaceOnly" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_run_placement_only">Setting this to True prevents the design from being routed. PAR will output a placed, but not routed Native Circuit Description (.ncd) file.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PAR_RunTimeReduction" href="/index.htm#context/ref/Run_Time_Reduction">This is a multi-seed PAR option that uses checkpoints for comparing the result of the current placement seed with the results already obtained. A placement seed that is not producing better results will automatically be terminated.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PAR_SLVS_MIPI_LVCMOS_OUTPUT" href="/index.htm#context/ref/par_slvs_mipi_lvcmos_output">This option allows the user to select between LVCMO12_18 ONLY (default)  or LVCMOS_NOT_PERMITTED.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PAR_StopZero" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_stop_once_timing_met">Setting this to True forces the Place and Route Design process to stop as soon as the timing requirement is satisfied. This option has no effect if the "Generate TRACE report for each iteration" option is set to True or if using Run Manager to produce multiple place-and-route runs.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PARSTA_AnalysisOption" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_analysis_options_for_place_route_trace_">Specifies the analysis type.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PARSTA_AutoTiming" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_auto_timing_for_place_route_trace_">Lists the auto-generated timing preferences in the TRACE report.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PARSTA_CheckUnconstrainedConns" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_check_unconstrained_connections_for_place_route_trace_">Reports connections not covered by a timing preference.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PARSTA_CheckUnconstrainedPaths" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_check_unconstrained_paths_for_place_route_trace_">Reports paths not covered by a timing preference.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PARSTA_FullName" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_full_name_for_place_route_trace_">When this is set to True, the TRACE report will show full-length component names instead of the truncated names.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PARSTA_NumUnconstrainedPaths" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_number_unconstrained_paths_for_place_route_trace_">Sets the maximum number of unconstrained paths that will be reported. "Unconstrained paths" are those not covered by a timing preference.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PARSTA_RptAsynTimLoop" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_report_asynchronous_timing_loops_for_place_route_trace_">Produces a report of paths that could not be analyzed because they are asynchronous loop.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PARSTA_ReportStyle" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_report_style_for_place_route_trace_">Specifies the type of the timing report.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PARSTA_SpeedForHoldAnalysis" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_speed_for_hold_analysis">Specifies performance grade for hold analysis. This option allows you to override the default m (minimum) performance grade for hold time analysis, which represents faster silicon than the fastest performance grade of the device being targeted.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PARSTA_SpeedForSetupAnalysis" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_speed_for_setup_analysis">Specifies performance grade for setup analysis. This option allows you to override the default performance grade which runs setup analysis against the performance grade of the device currently targeted by the project implementation.</description>
      <description name="PROP_PARSTA_WordCasePaths" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_worst_case_paths_0_4096_for_place_route_trace_">Specifies the number of paths to be reported for each timing preference. Enter zero or a grater value.</description>
      <description name="PROP_IOTIMING_AllSpeed" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_all_speed_grade">Controls whether the I/O timing report (.ior) will give an in-depth analysis on all available performance grades or will just produce a summary report on the worst-case performance grade.</description>
      <description name="PROP_TIM_TimSimGenPUR" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_generate_pur_in_the_netlist">When this is set to False, the timing simulation file generation process will not write PUR instance in the Verilog/VHDL backannotation netlist. Then you have to instantiate PUR in the test bench.</description>
      <description name="PROP_TIM_TimSimGenX" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_generate_x_for_setup_hold_violation">When this is set to True, the Timing Simulation process will place X notifiers in the output file on flip-flops with setup and/or hold time violations.</description>
      <description name="PROP_TIM_MinSpeedGrade" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_hold_check_min_speed_grade">Setting this to True replaces all timing information for back annotation with the minimum timing for all paths.</description>
      <description name="PROP_TIM_MaxDelSimDes" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_max_delay_bet_buffers_ps_">Distributes routing delays by splitting the signal and inserting buffers. The delay value assigned represents the maximum delay number in picoseconds between each buffer (1000 ps by default).</description>
      <description name="PROP_TIM_ModPreSimDes" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_multichip_module_prefix">Adds a prefix to module names to make them unique for multi-chip simulation.</description>
      <description name="PROP_TIM_NegStupHldTim" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_negative_setup_hold_times">Allows you to select negative setup time and negative hold time for better accuracy.</description>
      <description name="PROP_TIM_TrgtSpeedGrade" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_retarget_speed_grade">Retargets back annotation to a different performance grade than the one used to create the Native Circuit Description (.ncd) file.</description>
      <description name="PROP_TIM_TransportModeOfPathDelay" href="/index.htm#context/ref/Transport_Mode_of_Path_Delay_in_VHDL">When this is set to True, the VitalTransport glitch propagation type is used rather than the default OnDetect glitch propagation type.  This selection should be used to prevent filtering of a glitch when an input pulse is shorter than the propagation delay..</description>
      <description name="PROP_TIM_TimSimHierSep" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_verilog_hierarchy_separator">Specifies the hierarchy separator character which will be used in name generation when the design hierarchy is flattened.</description>
      <description name="PROP_TIM_WriteVerboseNetlist" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_write_verbose_netlist">When this is set to False (default), a parameterized netlist will be generated. The parameterized format contains less details, but is more compact in size and memory efficient within the simulator.</description>
      <description name="PROP_BIT_AddressBitGen" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_address">Specifies the bitstream addressing mode.</description>
      <description name="PROP_BIT_ByteWideBitMirror" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_byte_wide_bit_mirror">Reverses the order of the bits on a byte-by-byte basis.</description>
      <description name="PROP_BIT_ConModBitGen" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_chain_mode">When enabled, allows daisy chaining with other devices.</description>
      <description name="PROP_BIT_CreateBitFile" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_create_bit_file">When set to True, generates a bitstream file.</description>
      <description name="PROP_BIT_DisableUESBitgen" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_disable_ues">Excludes or includes the "User Electronic Signature Data" field in the JEDEC file.</description>
      <description name="PROP_BIT_EnIOBitGen" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_enable_i_o_in_re_configuration">When enabled, programs the FPGA to drive outputs (not be tristated) during configuration/reconfiguration. </description>
      <description name="PROP_TMCHK_EnableCheck" href="/index.htm#context/ref/Enable_Timing_Check">When this is set to true and there is timing error in the Place and Route report file, a dialogue box will display before executing bitstream generation.</description>
      <description name="PROP_BIT_ExtClockBitGen" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_external_clock">Used for testing Master configuration modes. </description>
      <description name="PROP_BIT_GranTimBitGen" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_grant_timeout">Controls an internal system bus grant counter that counts the number of HCLK (sysbus clk) cycles that go by before the grant signal is taken away from the master.</description>
      <description name="PROP_BIT_LenBitsBitGen" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_lengthbits">Specifies bitstream length.</description>
      <description name="PROP_BIT_NoHeader" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_no_header">When this is set to True, the header, or comment string, is not included in the bitstream.</description>
      <description name="PROP_BIT_OutFormatBitGen" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_output_format">Specifies the type of bitstream to create for an FPGA device.</description>
      <description name="PROP_BIT_RemZeroFramesBitGen" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_output_zero_frames">Controls whether zero frames are written to the output bitstream.</description>
      <description name="PROP_BIT_OutFormatPromGen" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_prom_data_output_format">Specifies the type of PROM data to create for an FPGA device.</description>
      <description name="PROP_BIT_ReadBackBitGen" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_readback">Controls whether the sysCONFIG readback operation will read from FLASH or SRAM.</description>
      <description name="PROP_BIT_ReadCaptureBitGen" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_readcapture">When this is enabled, the GLB is targeted during readback.</description>
      <description name="PROP_BIT_GSREnableBitGen" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_register_configuration">Controls whether the software will reset all flip-flops before reconfiguring the target FPGA. </description>
      <description name="PROP_BIT_DisRAMResBitGen" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_reset_config_ram_in_re_configuration">The Reset option reinitializes the device when you download a bitstream or JEDEC file. The No Reset option retains the current configuration and allows additional bitstream or JEDEC configuration.</description>
      <description name="PROP_BIT_DisRAMResBitGen2" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_reset_config_ram_in_re_configuration">The Reset option reinitializes the device when you download a bitstream or JEDEC file. The No Reset option retains the current configuration and allows additional bitstream or JEDEC configuration.</description>
      <description name="PROP_BIT_RunDRCBitGen" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_run_drc">When this is set to True, the software runs a physical design rule check and saves the output to the Bit Generation report file (.bgn).</description>
      <description name="PROP_BIT_SearchPthBitGen" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_search_path">Allows you to specify the search path of the auto-configuration file that is located in a directory other than the project directory.</description>
      <description name="PROP_BIT_SPIStartAddBitGen" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_spi_start_address">Specifies SPI start address.</description>
      <description name="PROP_BIT_StartUpClkBitGen" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_startup_clock">Controls whether to use CCLK or a User clock during startup.</description>
      <description name="PROP_BIT_SysClockConBitGen" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_sysbus_clock_config">Specifies either Reset or NoReset as the system bus clock at reconfiguration.</description>
      <description name="PROP_BIT_SysConBitGen" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_sysbus_config">Specifies either Reset or NoReset as the system bus at reconfiguration.</description>
      <description name="PROP_BIT_UFMOrder" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_UFM_order">Sets the order of the TAG memory content of LatticeXP2 devices. Normal is for TAG memories created with Diamond 3.0 or later. Legacy is for TAG memories created with Diamond 2.2 or earlier.</description>
      <description name="PROP_BIT_WaitStTimBitGen" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_wait_state_timeout">Controls an internal system bus timeout counter. The counter counts the number of HCLK (sysbus clk) cycles that go by while the system bus is in wait states.</description>
      <description name="PROP_BIT_XResCalibrationCtrl" href="/index.htm#context/ref/property_xres_calibration_control">Controls the calibration circuit connected to XRES pin.</description>
    </dialog>
  </tool>
</helpIndex>
