<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<helpIndex version="1.0">
  <tool name="POWER_CALC" href="/index.htm#context/user/analyzing_power_consumption">
    <dialog name="activity_factor" href="/index.htm#context/user/change_global_default_activity_factor">
      <whatsthis name="default">Specifies the global default activity factor. The default activity factory will appear in blue in the cells of the AF (%) column or where activity factor is used in calculations, such as Input AF (%).</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
    <dialog name="estimation_mode" href="/index.htm#context/user/estimate_routing_resource_usage">
      <whatsthis name="routing_resource_utilization">Specifies the relative amount of routing resources used by the design: low, medium, or high.</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
    <dialog name="freq_settings" href="/index.htm#context/user/changing_the_global_default_frequency_setting">
      <whatsthis name="default">Specifies the global default frequency. The default frequency will appear in the cells of the Freq.(MHz) column.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="use_twr">Uses the frequency settings from a selected trace report file (.twr). When you import this file, Power Calculator populates the Freq. (MHz) cells with the trace report settings.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="frequency_twr">Specifies the origin of the default frequency.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Minimum of Preference And Trace&lt;/b&gt; – The default frequency is taken from the lesser of the constrained frequency or the actual frequency in the Trace Report (.twr) file.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Always Use Preference&lt;/b&gt; – The default frequency is taken from the constrained frequency in the Trace Report (.twr) file.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Always Use Trace&lt;/b&gt; – The default frequency is taken from the actual frequency in the TRACE Report (.twr) file. </whatsthis>
    </dialog>
    <dialog name="graph_settings" href="/index.htm#context/user/generating_power_graphs"></dialog>
    <dialog name="implementation_compare" href="/index.htm#context/user/compare_power_among_implementations" />
    <dialog name="iotype_selection" href="/index.htm#context/user/editing_io_type" />
    <dialog name="new_project" href="/index.htm#context/user/creating_new_powercalc_file_in_stand_alone" />
    <dialog name="open_simulation_file" href="/index.htm#context/user/importing_a_vcd_file">
      <whatsthis name="vcd_file">Specifies the path and name of the .vcd file to import.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="module_name_in_vcd">Specifies the name of the module in the .vcd file from which to take frequency data. This module also contains the activity data with which to populate the columns that display activity data or that use an activity factor in calculations.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="case_sensitive">Select this box if the name of the .vcd file is case-sensitive.</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
    <dialog name="new_estimator_project" href="/index.htm#context/user/create_new_pwc_file_estimator" />
    <dialog name="power_average" href="/index.htm#context/user/obtain_average_power_over_time" />
    <dialog name="power_aware" href="/index.htm#context/user/compare_standby_results" />
    <dialog name="power_option_controller" href="/index.htm#context/user/enabling_power_options"></dialog>
    <dialog name="power_option_controller_ecp4" href="/index.htm#context/user/enabling_power_options_ecp4" />
    <dialog name="resource_settings" href="/index.htm#context/user/estimating_resource_usage" />
    <dialog name="startup_wizard" href="/index.htm#context/user/starting_powercalc_stand_alone"></dialog>
    <dialog name="thermal_profile" href="/index.htm#context/user/selecting_thermal_impedance_model">
      <whatsthis name="use_thermal_models">Calculates the effective thermal impedance value from the selections you make in the Board Selection, Heat Sink Selection, and Airflow Selection drop-down menus.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="use_defined_theta_ja">Enables you to specify your own effective thermal impedance value in the Effective Theta-JA box.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="board_selection">Specifies the type of board that you will be using.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="heat_sink_selection">Specifies the heat sink to be used.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="airflow_selection">Specifies the air flow in linear feet per minute (LFM) for the device.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="theta_sa_custom_heat_sink">Specify the value for your custom heat sink. This is available if you have selected Custom Profile Heat Sink from the Heat Sink Selection menu.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="effective_theta_ja">Specifies the effective thermal impedance value that can be used  for calculations. When "Use Thermal Models" is selected, Power Calculator calculates the value based on board, heat sink, and air flow selections. When "User Defined Effective Theta-JA" is selected, you can specify your own effective thermal impedance value.</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
  </tool>
</helpIndex>