<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<helpIndex version="1.0">
  <tool name="PACKAGE_VIEW" href="/index.htm#context/user/package_view">
    <dialog name="pin_display_select" href="/index.htm#context/user/filter_display_of_banks_pin_types">
      <whatsthis name="visible_banks">Displays the pins associated with the selected banks. When all banks are selected, pins that are not associated with a particular bank are visible, including SERDES, NC, GND, and VCC pins. "Others" indicates all banks that are not included in the listed visible banks.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="all_pios">Displays all I/O pins, including those with dual functions, plus PLL and clock pins.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="differential_+">Displays positive differential (TRUE) input or driver pins.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="differential_-">Displays negative differential input or driver pins.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="true_lvds">Displays pins that support differential output.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="emulated_lvds">Displays pins that support differential output through emulation, including LVDS, MLVDS, BLVDS, and LVPECL</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="vref">Displays voltage reference supply pins related to referenced input signal standards.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="pllck">Displays pins for PLL and DLL functions, including GPLL or SPLL input pins related to sysCLOCK PLL/DLL blocks.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="pllfb">Displays feedback pins for PLL and DLL functions, including GPLL or SPLL feedback input pins related to sysCLOCK PLL/DLL blocks.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="pclk">Displays primary clock input pins.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="dqs">Displays data strobe input pads for DDR interfaces. Any pin can be configured as an output.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="no_connect">Displays NC pins.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="serdes">Displays serializer/deserializer pins for SERDES block.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="jtag">Displays test and programming dedicated pins, including TMS, TCK, TDI, TDO, and VCCJ.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="vcc_vccio_vccaux_serdes">Displays power pins, including VCC, VCCIO, VCCAUX, and SERDES-related VCC pins.</whatsthis>
      <whatsthis name="gnd_gndio_vss">Displays ground pins.</whatsthis>
    </dialog>
  </tool>
</helpIndex>